SASWATA CHATTERJEE

S O F T W A R E E N G I N E E R



9007950520



chatterjeesaswata1997@gmail.com



Kolkata



https://fastidious-cranachan-5245b3.netlify.app/

PROFILE

Innovative and curious computer science engineering with a desire to always learn new things and apply them to real world scenarios in beneficial ways.

 $Skilled\ in\ JavaScript, Cs, HTML, Java\ and\ python\ and\ continuously\ trying\ to\ improve\ upon\ these\ , Also\ learning\ react\ .$

Committed to working as a collaborative and positive team member, striving to utilize my knowledge and expertise to optimize engineering results.

SKILLS

- · Web Design
- Javascript
- HTML/CSS
- JAVA
- Python
- React js
- · Problem-Solving
- Front End Coding

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Intelligent Inspiration

2020-2022

Monitored various automation processes and fixed errors in real time to ensure smooth flow of processes.

Occasionally wrote bash scripts to automate simple and redundant tasks . Solved error tickets and provided support.

DATA ANALYST

Globsyn 3rd life

2014 - 2016

Interned while in college as a data analyst was in charge of data annotation for Al models.

ACHIEVMENTS

Machine Learning Model 2019

Won best project award as a group for building a forest fire prediction model using python frameworks and machine learning .

LANGUAGES

English, Bengali, Hindi, Arabic,

German

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Elitte College of Engineering 2016-2020

ISC

St Augustine;s Day SChool **2016**

ICSE

St Augustine;s Day SChool **2014**